체스터스 밀은
여느 마을과
Chester's Mill is a place
like any other.
다를바가 없었다
At least, it used to be...
미스테리한 돔이 세상과
단절시키기 전까진 말이다
until we were cut off
from the rest of the world
by a mysterious dome.
(loud boom)
(cows bellowing)
투명하고 단단한데다
Invisible, indestructible,
도망갈 틈도 없었다
and completely inescapable.
우린 꼼짝없이 갇혔어
We're trapped.
어디서 나타나
LINDA: We don't know
where it came from
왜 이곳이어야만
했는진 모른다
or why it's here,
but now that we're all trapped
돔 안에 함께
갇힌 이상
under the dome together,
그 누구의 비밀도
안전할 순 없다
none of our secrets are safe.
그쪽은 누구시죠?
JULIA:
Who the hell are you?
절 바비라고 하더군요
BARBIE: Barbie. People
just call me Barbie.
제 별명이죠
It's a nickname.
제 남편과 별거 중이지만
My husband isn't here,
여기로 와 줄 거에요
but he'll turn up, you'll see.
프로판에 대해서
BIG JIM:
What do we do when the people
묻기 시작하면 어쩔건가?
start asking about the propane?
내 알바 아니지
That's your business.
(laughs)
심박 조율기에 이상있어요?
Duke, is it your pacemaker?
닥쳐!
(screams)
Stop!
악을 써도 소용없어
No one can hear us
all the way down here.
내보내 줘!
Let me out of here!
(screaming)
- 주니어
- 아빠
Junior.
Dad.
저희 집 구경시켜드리죠
You can stay with me.
Come on, I'll give you the nickel tour.
(grunts)
- 어디에 있지?
- 나한텐 없어
Where is it?
I don't have it!
보스가 무척이나
언짢아 할 거야
Yeah? My boss is not
gonna like that.
하루 줄게
You got one day.
알아들었지?
You hear me?
그쪽은 빚만
갚으면 된다고
Listen, all you've
got to do is pay up.
잘 생각 좀
해봐, 알겠지?
You might want to think
about it, all right?
섣부른 행동 말고
I mean, you don't want
to do anything stupid.
(grunting)
(gunshot)
(loud exhale)
(knocking on door)
들어오세요
Yeah?
괜찮으세요?
You all right?
네, 괜찮습니다
Yep. Fine.
잠꼬대 하시던데요
You were, uh,
talking in your sleep.
악을 쓰면서요
Yelling, actually.
그게 아직도 있나요?
Is that thing still out there?
그럴거에요
Yeah, looks like it.
독극물 처리반이
남아 있더군요
The Hazmat suits haven't left.
줄리아
Julia...
절 재워주셔서 감사합니다
thanks again
for letting me crash here.
남편이 실종되고
With my husband missing,
별일이 다 있었지만
and everything
that happened today...
당신이 곁에
있어서 안심됐어요
it was nice to have the company.
주무세요
I'll see you in the morning.
그러죠
Great.
뭘 찾고 계시나요?
Did you lose something?
네, 제 군번줄을
Yeah. You didn't
happen to see
못 보셨나 해서요?
a pair of dog tags
around anywhere, did you?
네
No.
찾아 볼게요
But I'll keep an eye out.
쉬세요
Night.
(siren wailing)
린다? 린다!
Linda! Linda!
무슨 일이야?
What the hell happened?
누가 서장님을 쏜거야?
Who shot Duke?
그런거 아니니까 침착하세요
No one shot Duke, Paul.
Calm down.
이 물체에
가까이 다가가자
He just got close
to this thing,
심박 조율기가 폭발했어요
and his pacemaker exploded.
Ah!
- 세상에
- 만약 이 물체가
Holy...
If this thing
기계를 폭발시킨다면
blows up mechanical things,
프레디의 시계는
왜 멀쩡한거지?
then why didn't
Freddy's watch explode?
수동이잖아요
It's a wind-up.
배터리로 돌아가는 거에
영향을 미치나봐요
It must only affect things
with batteries.
어쨌든 봉쇄로를 확인하고
Either way,
just check the roadblocks
이것 근처에도
못가게 하세요
and make sure nobody gets
near this thing.
누가 서장님을 대신하지?
Well, who's in charge now?
경찰의 본분이나 다 하세요
You're a cop. Do your job.
그럼 나는?
What about me?
여기 있어줘
We need to take care of Duke.
조, 기다려
BEN:
Joe, wait up!
괜찮대도
I'm fine.
웃기지마
No, you're not.
한시간 전에
발작을 일으켰었잖아
An hour ago,
you were having a seizure,
낚인 물고기 마냥
뒤집어져서 말야
flopping around
like a fish on a hook.
내가 뭔 말 하던?
Did I say anything?
별에 대해서 말하더라고
Yeah, something about... stars.
분홍별말야
Pink stars.
숨기는거 있어?
Anything you want to tell me?
아니
No.
저기요
JOE:
Hey!
좋은 소식 있으세요?
Any luck, you guys?
아직은 멀었어
No, not yet!
더 파봐야 알겠지
This thing goes down far.
그게 무슨 뜻인지 알아?
Oh, my God, you know
what all this means?
내일 삼각법 시험을
안보게 생겼다는 거야
We're so not having
that trig test tomorrow.
삼각법이라
Trig.
그거 참 좋은 생각인데
That's a great idea.
정말로?
It is?
규모를 짐작할
수 있겠어
I can totally map this thing,
출구도 말야
see if there's any holes.
같이 가 줄게
I'm coming with you.
안 그래도 돼
Dude, you don't have to.
너한텐 내가
있잖아, 알겠지?
Buddy, Lewis had Clark,
you got me, all right?
같이 가
Come on.
(rock music plays)
있잖아
Say...
네가 만든
기계 넘어로
did you hear anything more
about the military
- 군바리들이 뭐라 하던?
- 아니
on that contraption of yours?
DODEE: Nope.
주파수를 다시
맞추고 있어
I lost the signal,
but I'm trying to get it back.
그게 그렇게 쉬운
일은 아니거든
It's not as easy as cuing up
the next Van Halen track.
엔지니어가 DJ
보다 우월한거지?
Now, why is it that engineers
always act superior to DJs?
우리가 더 똑똑하니까, 필
Because we're smarter, Phil.
아닙니다
MAN:
Negative, sir,
화염에도 표면엔
이상이 없었습니다
fire is ineffective
against the surface.
돔이 방사성 물질을
발산하진 않는다는걸
But we can confirm
there is no radioactivity
확인했습니다
emanating from the dome.
또 그러네
They did it again.
하루사이에 두번이나
돔이라고 하다니
Second time in 24 hours
they called it a dome.
응, 나도 들었어
Yeah, I heard him.
No, I don't think you did,
그러기엔 너무 담담한데
because you'd be
freaking out, too.
우린 돔 안에 갇혔다고
We're under a dome, Dodee.
이건 단순히
투명한 벽이 아냐
Now, this is not just
some invisible wall
헬기도 우릴 구하러
올 수 조차 없어
where a chopper can drop
in and rescue us, man.
주민들 한테도 알려야해
We gotta tell people.
그럴건데
And we will.
지금은 시기상조야
It's just right now
we only know enough
괜히 공포감만
조성하게 될 거야
to scare the crap out of them.
채널고정하시라
To be continued.
♪
♪ Up to second gear,
then come back down ♪
♪ Daddy call his boss...
(music cuts out)
여러분을 위해 깨어있는
필 부쉬 인사드립니다
Faithful insomniacs,
Phil Bushey here.
기나 긴 밤이었습니다
It's been a long night.
지금도 듣고 계신다면
And if you're listening to me,
어쩔수가 없어서겠죠
it's because
you've got no choice.
이 장벽이
You see, this barrier thing
휴대폰은 물론
is blocking
all of the cell phones,
TV, 인터넷을 차단시켰습니다
TV, Internet...
체스터스 밀 통채로 말이죠
everything in our humble burg
of Chester's Mill.
이 배후에는
Now, theories about
what's causing this
북한이 있다고들 하는데요
range from the North Koreans
시공연속체에 틈을 내서
to a breach
in the space-time continuum...
빨리 왔어야 했는데, 로즈
BIG JIM: Well, sorry I didn't
get to you sooner, Rose.
진료소하고
Had to make sure the clinic
요양소에 들러봐야 했거든요
and the nursing home
were taken care of.
그걸 말이라고 하세요?
선물만 가져오면
Are you kidding me?
If you're not careful,
사람들이 의원님을
산타할아버지라고 부르겠어요
people are gonna start
calling you Santa Claus.
(sighs)
당신 밖에 없어요, 짐 레니.
Oh, God bless you, Jim Rennie.
어떻게 보상해 드리죠?
How much do I owe you?
Ho, ho, ho.
전기가 다시 들어왔잖아
Oh, my God.
The lights are back.
투명한 벽이 없어졌나요?
Did that invisible wall
come down?
그럴리가 있겠습니까만
Well, I'm afraid not.
비상용 발전기를
작동시키고 있어서
But, uh, we've got gennies
up and running,
전기가 들어온 겁니다
so we have some power,
임시로 말이죠
at least get back to
some sense of normal.
처음 뵙는 분이신데
I don't believe we've met.
짐 레니 의원님
이쪽은 캐롤린
ROSE: Councilman Jim
Rennie, this is Carolyn
파트너 앨리스예요
and, uh, her partner Alice.
윗층 손님방에서
머물고 계시죠
They're staying
in my spare room upstairs.
LA에서 오셨대요
They're in from L.A.
이 마을을 지나가다가
갇히게 됐어요
We got trapped driving
through your little town.
딸 노리를 캠프에
데려다 주려고요
We were taking our daughter Norrie to...
To camp.
여기서 나가야만 해요
But we have to get out of here.
딸이 아프거든요
Our daughter is sick.
발작을 일으켜요
She had a seizure.
따님께서 간질을
앓고 있나요?
Does your girl have epilepsy?
발작의 원인은 여러가지죠
ALICE:
No. It can happen to anyone.
카페인 과다섭취나
Caffeine,
잠이 모자랄 경우에요
sleep deprivation.
제가 보던
환자가 그랬거든요
I've seen it in my patients.
정신과 의사거든요
She's a psychiatrist.
체스터스 밀에서 이런일을
Well, I'm sorry you ladies
겪게 해드려
죄송합니다만
aren't discovering
Chester's Mill
제가 장담하는데
under better circumstances,
but trust me,
그 어디에
발이 묶여도
if you're gonna be
stuck somewhere,
이만한 곳은 없을겁니다
this is the place to be.
제 평생을 여기
살아봐서 아는데
I've lived here my entire life,
and, uh...
(bell jingles)
제 고향만한
곳은 없더군요
...no place
I'd rather call home.
짐
Jim.
저랑 어딜 좀 가시죠
I need you to come with me.
서장님이 돌아가셨어요
Duke's dead.
날 좀 보라고
Look at me, damn it!
안보겠다?
Anyone?
신경도 안쓸겁니다
I wouldn't even bother.
(sighs)
당신이 알몸으로 나타나도
I mean, you could strip naked
in front of these guys,
눈길 조차
주질 않을겁니다
they're still not
gonna pay attention.
그건 이미 해 봤는데
I tried that an hour ago.
눈 하나 깜짝
안하더라고요
They didn't even blink.
Oh.
주변을 둘러봤는데
I looked around, by the way,
군번은 못찾았어요
but no sign of your dog tags.
괜찮습니다
Oh, yeah, no worries.
You know what?
제 차에 있겠죠
I probably just left
them in my car.
왜 저희와
So what makes you think
말섞지 않는거 같으세요?
these guys are under orders
not to talk to us?
저희한테
말을 안거니까요
Because they're
not talking to us.
이들 짓일 거에요
Maybe they did this, you know.
저들한테 책임이 있겠죠
Maybe they're responsible.
뭣 하러요?
And why would they do that?
모르죠
I don't know.
실험하려고요
Could be, uh, an experiment.
간이용 수용소에
Some sort of portable
detention camp.
실험쥐가 필요했나보죠
Maybe we're being used
as guinea pigs.
이유가 어찌됐든
Whatever it is,
these guys are the reason
내 남편이 이 밖에서
my husband is trapped
못들어 오고 있잖아!
out there!
(exhales)
어디 가시게요?
ere you heading?
라디오 방송국이요
The radio station.
상대가 우리가 아니라면
They might not
be talking to us,
다른 누군가가 있겠죠
but they are talking
to somebody.
(car door closes)
(locks clanking)
나랑 같이 있으면
안전할 거라 했잖아
I told you, you're safe with me.
레니 아저씨!
Mr. Rennie!
(muffled):
살려주세요!
(banging)
Help! Help!
- 레니 아저씨!
- 앤지
Mr. Rennie!
Angie...
우리 아빤
집에 안계셔
my dad's not home.
Mr. Rennie!
레니 아저씨!
(screaming):
Mr. Rennie!
아빤 집에 안계신다고!
My dad's not home!
(screaming)
날 놔줘
Mr. Rennie!
Let go of me!
놔달라고
Let go!
안돼
No... no!
싫어
No!
안돼
No! No!
Ah! N...
저리 가
(grunting):
Get... off.
가버려
(grunts)
Get...
도대체 나한테
왜 이러는 거야?
(panting)
What the hell do you want from me?
내가 알던
어제의 앤지를
Look, I just want you
to go back to being
되찾고 싶어서
the Angie I knew
before yesterday.
잘 지내다가
We were doing great,
이 물체가
and then this thing
나타나자마자
comes down and you...
날 찼잖아
00:09:38,034 -> 00:09:39,835
그것 때문에 네 머리가
어떻게 됐나봐
you tell me to take a hike.
I think it scrambled your brain.
사돈남말하지마
One of us has a scrambled brain,
all right.
넌 모르는 뭔가를
난 알고 있어
You can't see it, but I can.
(sighs)
네가 아파서
그래, 앤지
You're sick, Angie.
내가 낫게 해 줄게
But I'm gonna make you better.
내가 중환자라면
If I'm so sick,
병원에 입원시키지 그래?
then why don't you take me
to the hospital?
내가 그렇게
걱정된다면 말야
If you care about me so much?
그놈이 거기에
있을지도 모르잖아
Because he might
still be there.
누가 거기에
있을지도 모른다고?
Who might still be here?
너랑 같이 있던 놈말야
The guy I saw you with.
누구말야?
What guy?
어제
Yesterday?
병원 밖에 서 있던
Outside the hospital?
바비말야
Barbie?
셤웨이 부인과
함께 왔던 남자?
The guy who came in
with Mrs. Shumway?
생전 처음
보는 남자였어
I don't even know him.
날 속일 생각마
Don't play dumb with me, Ange,
뻔히 보이니까
I can see right through you.
담배 한 대
빌린 게 다야
All he did was
give me a cigarette.
Uh-huh.
내가 뭘
그렇게 잘못했니?
What did I ever do to you?!
날 사랑했잖아
You loved me.
아냐
No.
주니어
Junior...
- 그런적 없어
- 사랑했잖아
I never...
Yes, Angie, you did.
그 물체가 없어지면
And when this thing comes down,
날 다시
사랑하게 될거야
you're gonna love me again.
널 사랑했던 적은
단 한번도 없었어
I will never love you!
네 말이 맞아
You were right.
병원에 있던
That guy...
그 남자랑
at the hospital,
담배만 나눠
핀게 아냐
we didn't just share
a cigarette.
존나게 떡도 쳤어
He screwed my brains out,
좋았었어
and I loved it.
너랑 했을 때보다 더
I loved it more
than I ever did with you.
죽었다 깨어나도
넌 그렇게 못 할거야
You'll never be the man
that he is.
주니어!
Junior!
한글자막 DC기미갤 PEH
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
이럴수가
BIG JIM:
Holy hell.
괜찮은 놈이었는데
He was a good man.
아끼던 분이셨죠
I loved him.
아버지 같은 분이셨어요
He was like a father to me.
좋은 친구였어
He was a good friend.
돌아가시기 전에
You know, just before he died,
뭔가 할말이 있으시댔어요
he tried to tell me something.
(sighs)
뭘 말인가?
Tried telling you what?
체스터스 밀에 대해
He said there were things
제가 모르고
있는 걸요
that I didn't know
about Chester's Mill.
저한테 비밀로
했던 걸요
Things that he needed
to protect me from.
그게 무슨 뜻이죠?
What did that mean?
알았으면 좋으련만
I wish I could tell you.
(sighs)
나보고 어쩌라는 건가?
What am I gonna do
with another body?
냉장고는 만원이니
The cemetery is
outside the barrier,
묘지에다 묻게나
and my freezer's full.
고인에게 그게
할 소린가
BIG JIM:
Show some respect.
딴사람도 아닌
This isn't just another body.
듀크 퍼킨스잖나
This is Duke Perkins.
뭐라고?
What's that?
보청기를 켜, 레스터
Turn up your hearing aid,
Lester.
듀크 퍼킨스라고
I said this is Duke Perkins.
안돼
Oh, no.
하늘도 무심하시지
Oh, good Lord. He's Duke Perkins.
에스키벨 부보안관
Deputy Esquivel,
이렇게 된 거 유감일세
I'm so sorry for your loss.
감사합니다
코긴스 목사님
Thank you, Reverend Coggins.
전 가봐야겠습니다
I should get back out there.
린다, 가서
도리를 다 하게나
Well, you're right, Linda.
Go out there and do your job.
듀크는 내가
알아서 할테니
I'll make sure Duke here
gets taken care of.
(door opens, closes)
우리걸 썼군
You're using our stuff.
취해가지곤
You're high as a kite.
세상의 종말이 찾아왔으니
So what? It's Judgment Day, Jim.
황홀경은 맛보고 죽어야지
I might as well be feeling
the Rapture.
이 일에 발을
들여놓은 이유는
The only reason we got into this
체스터스 밀을
구하기 위해서였잖나
was to try to save
Chester's Mill.
아니
No.
그건 듀크였잖나
That's the reason Duke went
along with it.
자네와 난 다른
볼일이 있어서였고
You and I,
we had other priorities.
알겠나?
(grunts)
All right?
내 말은
I mean...
적어도 지금은
I mean, at least now,
그자가 발설할
걱정은 없잖는가
we don't have to worry
about him talking.
천생 목사군
Real man of God there, Rev.
어서 가보세
Come on, let's go.
어디로 말인가?
What? Where are we going?
뒷정리를 하러
Clean up our mess.
(paint can hissing)
출구를 찾았어
Dude, found a way out.
봐봐
Check it.
너도 참 못말린다
(chuckles)
You're such an idiot.
(laughs)
너가 조지?
It's Joe, right?
네, 맥앨리스터 씨
Yeah, McAlister.
비행기가 충돌할 당시
Dude, this is the
guy who saved my ass
날 살려주셨던 분이셔
when that plane went down.
팔다리가 비오듯
쏟아졌다는데요
He totally said
it was raining arms and legs.
그랬었지
Yeah, you could say that.
뭘 하고 있었니?
What are you up to?
삼각법을 이용했어요
So far, I marked these points,
두변의 거리를 재서
and by measuring the distance
between them,
Y의 좌표를 알 수 있죠
I was able to come up
with the Y coordinate,
K정수를 그 값에 곱하면
and then by multiplying it
by its K integer...
점을 연결하고 있었어요
He connected the dots.
원이 그려지더군요
It's totally gonna be circle.
폭이 10마일에
달하는거 같아요
So far, it looks like
it's about ten miles across.
이 마을 전체를
둘러싸고 있죠
It covers the entire Mill,
이스트포인트
호수의 일부분도요
including some
of Lake Eastpointe.
너가 알아낸거니?
And you did this?
네, 근데
조심하고 있어요
Yeah, but we're being
really careful.
마져해
Keep it up.
어디 출신이야?
Where'd that guy come from?
여기 출신은 아닐거야
Definitely not from around here.
어딜 봐서?
How do you know?
쿨하잖아
'Cause he's cool.
도티, 다 됐잖아
Come on, Dodee,
you just had him.
좀 기다려봐, 필립
Patience, Philip.
(radio static, muffled voices)
찾아낸거야?
Did you get something?
Shh.
추후공지가 있기 전까진
체스터스 밀 상공의
MAN: Air traffic has been
rerouted around Chester's Mill
항로를 변경한다
until further notice.
영공을 계속 감시하라
Continue to monitor
the airspace.
방금 뭐라고 한거죠?
JULIA:
What the hell is that?
(papers rustling)
짐?
(sighs)
Jim.
뭐하시는 거에요?
What are you doing?
난
I was, um,
이걸 찾고 있었지
looking for that.
서장님의 유언장이군요
It's Duke's will.
읽어봐
Go ahead, read it.
(sniffles)
서장님께서
He, uh,
제 앞으로
집을 남기셨네요
left me his house.
전부를요
Everything.
그랬겠지
Of course he did.
(sniffling)
자넬 딸 처럼 여겼잖나
He treated you like the daughter
he never had.
(sobbing)
이제 어떻게 하죠?
Now what do we do?
자네 덕분에
It was a close call.
걸릴 뻔 했잖나
No thanks to you.
그럼 전화라도 해주리?
What was I supposed to do,
phone you?
뭘 알아낸건가?
So what'd you find out?
프로판에 관한건 없었네
Nothing to do with propane.
듀크라면 집에다 숨겨놨을걸세
Duke must have kept the records
at his house.
이젠 그놈의
집이 아니더라고
Yeah, but it's not
his house anymore.
유산으로
부서장한테 줬어
He left it to the girl.
자네가 먼저
So you better get over there
선수를 처야해
before she does.
Me?
나보고 어쩌라는 건가?
What are you gonna do?
알아서 해, 레스터
My job, Lester.
내리라고
Now get out.
난 체스터스 밀에
유일한 의원이잖나
I'm the only councilman
left in Chester's Mill.
그렇게 한가한
사람이 아니라네
(engine starts)
I got a town to take care of.
그쪽이 만든거에요?
JULIA:
You made this?
3학점 부족해서
DODEE: Yeah, I'm only
three credits short
전기공학과 석사학위를
못 받았죠
of my master's degree
in electrical engineering.
어떻게 작동하는거죠?
Wow. How does it work?
이건 조화 극초단파
주파수 변환기인데요
Well, this is a harmonic
microwave frequency converter.
저주파를 고주파로
변환해 주는거죠
It turns low frequency waves
into high frequency waves
알아듣게 말해줄래요?
so that we can hear them.
Maybe you should just
let me hear it?
그러죠
Okay.
찾기가 힘들어요
Um, sometimes it's
hard to pick up.
(static, muffled voices)
추후 시행된 검사로
MAN:
Further tests reveal
돔은 고출력 레이저와
dome appears to be impervious
A급 부식성 화학약품에
to high energy lasers
불투성인 것이 밝혀졌다
and all class-A
corrosive chemicals.
돔 안에 갇혔군요
We're under a dome.
그렇게 부르더라고요
Yeah, that's what
they keep calling it.
왜 숨기고 있었던거죠?
Why haven't you told anybody?
뉴스 보도국이 아니잖아요
We're not a news station.
필?
Hey, Phil?
끝내주는 락을
한 곡을 들으셨습니다
And that was some
face-melting rock and roll
제가 좀 할게요
brought to you by...
I'm going on.
막무가내야
I tried to stop her.
- 죄송한데 뭘요?
- 제가 방송에 나가겠다고요
I'm sorry, what are you doing?
I'm going on the air.
안돼요
No, you can't.
인디펜던트 지의
줄리아 셤웨이입니다
This is Julia Shumway
from the weekly Independent.
체스터스 밀에
발이 묶인
I have some news for all of us
이유에 관해
말씀해 드리겠습니다
stuck here inside
Chester's Mill.
체스터스 밀 주변을
I have just learned
that the barrier
감싼 장벽을
around Chester's Mill
돔이라고 부르는걸
듣게 되었습니다
is being called a dome.
체스터스 밀 밖에
배치 돼 있는
This information appears
to be coming
군관계 인사에게서
from military sources
들은 내용입니다
positioned just
outside Chester's Mill,
돔 밖으로 정정합니다
just outside the dome.
소식이 들어오는대로
전해드리도록 하겠습니다
We will keep updating you
as information comes in.
채널고정하세요
So stay tuned to...
WYBS였습니다
WYBS.
돔 안에서 뉴스를
보도하는 유일한 곳
Your only source of news
from under the dome.
(clicks)
(sighs)
무슨 뜻이야?
What does that mean?
글쎄다
I have no idea.
전 알 거 같아요
I do, Mom.
여기서 다
죽을거란 뜻이에요
It means we're all gonna die
in here.
이 돔이라는게 규모가
어떻게 되는거죠?
ROSE: This dome
thing, how big is it?
모릅니다
No idea.
돔안에 갇힌거에요?
We're under a dome?
Are we gonna run
산소가 부족해 지겠네요
out of air?
Until I find out
줄리아에게 확인을
해 보기 전까진
where Julia got
this information,
평정을 유지하시기 바랍니다
I think it's best
that we just all stay calm.
그게 무너져 내린다면요?
What if it collapses on us?
이젠 하늘까지 무너지는구나
Great, now the sky is falling.
조심하면서 합심한다면
If we keep our heads
and we stick together,
이겨낼 수 있습니다
we'll get through this.
이겨낼 수 있을 거라고?
(bell jingles)
Hey, "We'll get through this"?
이 돔이라는걸
잘 알지도 못하잖아?
Huh? You don't know what
this dome thing might do.
잘모르지만, 일단은
마을 분들을 진정시켜야죠
You're right, but the last
thing we need right now
is for people to panic.
That thing took Duke.
그게 서장님을 죽였잖아
다음은 누구 차롄데?
Who's next?
마음을 추스르고
순찰이나 도세요
Pull yourself together
and get out on patrol.
사람들이 겁에 질리면
People are scared, and
when people are scared,
정신나간 짓을
하기 마련이니까요
they start acting stupid.
겁에 안 질리려면
정신나간 짓을 해야겠네
Yeah, you'd have to be stupid
not to be scared.
내 바람은 누군가가
You know,
I just hope someone tries
이 좆같은 걸
날려버렸음 속시원하겠어
to blow this damn thing up.
(car sensor dinging)
(engine starts)
괜찮을까?
Do you think
he's gonna be okay?
그래야지
He's got to be.
남은 인력도 없잖아
We're gonna need
every man we got.
(sighs)
(bell jingles)
다시 만날 수 있을까?
Think we'll ever see him again?
누구? 러스티?
Who, Rusty?
왜 그래, 린다
Come on, Linda.
우리 형은 말야
My brother's not gonna let
마법의 물방울을 뚫고
some magic bubble thing
널 데릴러 올거야
keep him from seeing you again.
맞아, 그래야 러스티답지
Yeah, that is Rusty.
그거 알아?
Hey, you know what?
비밀로 했어야 했겠지만
I probably shouldn't be
telling you this,
하와이로 허니문
가려고 했었어
but he's taking you to Hawaii
for your honeymoon.
나이아가라 폭포나
보러 간다고 했는데
That dog told me that I had
to settle for Niagara Falls.
목사님
Reverend.
헤이
Hey.
잘 버티고 있나?
How you holding up?
힘들어도 버텨야죠
We got our hands full,
but I think we'll make it.
자넬 위해 기도하겠네
Yeah, you're in my prayers.
줄리아 셤웨이가 전해드립니다
Julia Shumway,
back with an update.
추가적으로 입수된
정보에 의하면
Additional reports suggest
that the dome
돔은 방사성
물질이 아니지만
is not radioactive,
주민분들께선
but residents are advised
접근을 삼가해
주시기를 바랍니다
to continue to keep
a safe distance.
이제는
PHIL: And now, something
to take our minds
한 숨 돌릴
수 있겠군요
off all this trouble.
What? (horn honking)
헤이
(rock music playing on radio)
Hey!
(horn honking)
(turns off engine, music stops)
헤이, 거기 서
Hey! Hey, stop! Stop!
뭐하는 짓인가?
What the hell are you doing?
땅파서 나가려고 하네
I'm digging my way out.
안될세
No, you're not.
뭐하자는 건가?
What the hell?
돔이 기계에
닿기만 한다면
Any machine touches that dome,
자넨 통구이가
될 걸세
you're fried.
- 누가 그러는데?
- 듀크의
Says who?
Duke.
심박 조율기가 폭발해서
His pacemaker blew right
out of his chest.
죽었어
He's dead.
듀크가 죽었다고?
Duke's dead?
그럼 누가 책임잔데?
Who's in charge?
여기서 영원히
못빠져 나간다면?
What if we're trapped
in here forever?
밀라 쿠니스랑
떡 못치겠지
I'll never get to make out
with Mila Kunis.
그 이유말고도
I don't think this thing
이유는 여러가지가 있겠지
is the only thing keeping
that from happening.
생각 좀 해봐
Just think about it.
여자도 못 만나보고
죽다니 억울하잖아
We could have met every girl
we're ever gonna meet.
암울하네
That is so depressing.
뭐하는 거지?
What the hell?
시험을 하는거야
JOE:
They're doing tests.
물이 통과하는지 말야
Must be checking to see
if water can come through.
불길한데
우린 좆됐구나
Doesn't look good.
We're screwed.
어디보자
Wait.
체로 거른거 같아
It's like a sieve.
체가 뭔데?
What the hell's a sieve?
거르개말야
A strainer, douche.
파스타 건질때 안써?
Like-like for pasta?
그럼 물이
통과한다는 말이야?
So it does let water through?
조금은
Yeah, just a little.
우리도 통과할 수 있겠다
Maybe we can get through.
사람의 몸은 70%가
물로 돼 있잖아?
Aren't we, like, 70% water?
남은 30%가
문제지, 똑똑아
Yeah, it's the other 30%
that's the problem, genius.
이거하고 필터 달린걸로
한 팩 주시겠어요?
This and, uh, can you give
me a pack of filtered?
그냥 세갑만 주세요
Actually, you know what?
Make it three.
그게 다에요?
Anything else?
네
No, that's it.
(cash register beeping)
고맙습니다
Thank you.
(bell jingles)
담배피면 몸에 해롭다고
안그러던가요?
Didn't anyone ever tell you
smoking's bad for you?
내가 필게 아니란다
Hey, no,
these-these aren't for me.
만약을 위해서지
It's an investment.
여기에 영영
못나가게 된다면
We end up getting stuck
in here for a while,
you would be surprised
물물교환하는
일이 생기겠지
what people will swap
for these things.
에너지 바도
안먹는게 좋을거야
So I'd probably hang onto
that candy bar if I were you.
(scoffs)
전에는 됐었잖아요
JULIA: What's wrong?
You had it working before.
차에 달린
라디오 처럼
DODEE:
It's not like punching in
한 대 친다고
되는게 아니라고요
the presets on your car radio.
This takes finesse.
웃기고 있네
뻥치는 거에요
Finesse, my ass.
She's just diddling.
운이 좋았던거죠
Sometimes she gets lucky.
추후 시행된 검사로
MAN: Further tests
reveal the dome appears
돔은 고출력 레이저에
불투성인 것이 밝혀졌다
to be impervious
to high-energy laser.
이래도 운이야?
How's that for lucky?
Shh.
지상기동 2부대다
This is Mobile Ground Unit 2.
철저한 검사를 마쳤지만
우린 돔의 기원도
After exhaustive testing we are
unable to determine the origin
구성성분도 밝혀내지 못했다
or the composition of the dome.
세상에
Oh, my God,
군에서도 뭔지 모르는구나
the military doesn't know
what it is.
그래서요?
So?
군의 짓이 아니라는 거죠
So it means they didn't do it.
그들의 탓이 아니에요
They're not responsible.
그럼요?
Who is?
(hinges creak)
(gun clicks)
비어있군
Empty.
(clip clicks into gun)
어디에 있는거야
Come on. Come on.
헤이
Hey.
여기서 뭐하시나?
What have you got there?
날 미행한거냐?
Why are you following me?
여기가 거기군
So, this is where you did it.
도대체 무슨
소릴 지껄이는거냐?
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
걔랑 떡친데잖아
This is where you screwed her.
앤지와 네놈이 바람폈었잖아
I know all about you and Angie.
앤지가 누군데?
Who's Angie?
시치미 떼지마
Don't act like you don't know.
한 판 뒹굴었나본데
Looks like she put up
a pretty good fight.
걘 내꺼야
She belongs to me.
걔도 참 불쌍하다
That's too bad for her.
(growls)
(grunting)
걘 내꺼라고
She still belongs to me.
내 앞에
얼씬거리지도 마
You just stay
the hell away from me.
안그러면?
Or what?
다음엔 봐주지 않겠어
The next time,
I'm not gonna stop.
(hinges creak)
Ah!
(chuckles)
Ah...
주님이 하시는 일은
아무도 모르지
The Lord works
in mysterious ways.
(chuckles)
(gasps)
Ah-ah! Ah!
Ah!
안돼, 주여 도와주소서
Help! No! Lord, help!
(barking)
(dog whines)
맨
Aw, man.
개 주인이
저기에 있었나봐
His master must've been
right here.
누군가 상체만
끌고 갔고
Someone must've dragged
the rest of the body away.
(dog whines)
불쌍하다
JOE:
Poor fella.
개가 불쌍하다고?
The dog's the poor fella?
개 주인이
더 안째 같은데
I kind of feel sorrier
for the cut-in-half dude.
트루맨이라는데
His name's Truman.
그래서 어떻게 하려고?
What're we gonna do with him?
두고 갈 순 없잖아
We can't just leave him here.
세상에, 저길 봐봐
Holy crap. Look.
불이 났네
A fire.
가서 보자
Let's go check it out.
가자, 트루맨
Come on, Truman!
(tires squealing)
죽을 뻔 했잖아요
You almost killed us!
뭘 좀 가져왔어
PAUL:
I got something for you.
폴, 제정신이야?
Paul, what are you thinking?
이 마을은 까딱하면
무법도시가 될 거라고
This town is one click away from
total and complete lawlessss.
그 때를
대비해 둔거지
When the time comes, I'm ready,
너도 대비해
두는게 좋을거다
and you should be, too.
우린 같은 편이잖아
We're on the same side here.
지금 당장은 말이지
Yeah, for now.
(shotgun racks)
뭐하는 놈이야?
Who the hell are you?!
괜찮아요, 저분께서
Easy. That's the guy
비행기 추락할 때
that saved the McAlister kid
맥앨리스터 아들을 구했어요
when the plane
crashed in the dome.
린다, 응답하라
JACKIE:
Linda, you there?
밖으로 나와 봐
Get out here so I can
see you. Come here.
무슨 일이야, 재키
Go ahead, Jackie.
사라 마틴이
Sarah Martin just drove over.
프리티 밸리 로드
223번지에서 불이 났대
She says there's a fire
at 223 Pretty Valley Road.
서장님 자택이잖아
Oh, my God, that's Duke's house.
남는 인력을
그곳으로 출동시켜
Get every warm body out there
to help.
체스터스 밀
관할 소방관들은
You can kiss it good-bye--
the entire Chester's Mill's
우리와 달리
이 너머에 있잖아
fire department's out there
and we're in here.
총 내리고
서장님 댁으로 가요
Put that rifle down
and get your ass to Duke's.
넌 서장이 아니잖아
You're not my boss.
당장요
Now.
그쪽도 타세요
You, warm body. Get in.
소방차가 한 대도 없나?
PAUL (over scanner):
Any fire trucks still here?
러스티와 대원들이 소방차를
끌고 웨스트레이크로
LINDA: Rusty and his buddies
took them all to Westlake
퍼레이드에 참석하러 갔다
for that damn parade.
서장님 댁으로 출동하라
Clear the line
and get to Duke's.
망할, 코닝스
Damn it, Coggins.
(tires squeal)
소방차는 왜
안오는 거죠?
WOMAN:
Where's the fire department?
여기에요
MAN:
Right over here! Come on!
지금 오고 있습니다
MAN 2:
Right now, they're coming.
물러서십쇼!
Hey, stay back! Stay back!
물러서세요!
Stay back!
사람 살려요!
COGGINS:
Help! Help!
절 좀 도와주세요!
Somebody, somebody help me!
(sirens approach)
비켜요!
MAN:
Get out of the way!
(sirens stop)
여긴 왠일이세요?
What are you doing here?
불이 났다길래
I heard it on the scanner.
- 무슨 일이죠?
- 낸들 알겠나
What happened?
I have no idea.
듀크가 혼자
살았으니 망정이지
I'm just glad Duke lived alone.
뒤로 물러나주십쇼
FREDDY: Come on. Everyone,
please stand back.
안전거리를 유지하세요
Come on.
Keep a safe distance.
불을 꺼야겠어요
We have to put this out.
어떻게 끄자는 건데?
How the hell are we gonna
do that?
수압기 다들 있으시죠?
You guys still got your
water pressure, right?
정원에 있는
호스를 가져오세요
So, go and get as many
garden hoses as you can.
- 서두르세요
- 호스가 필요합니다
Go. Go-go-go-go-go-go.
Hey, guys, we need hoses.
가서 물 받아 오세요
Go. Go get water.
호스 가지고 있는 분?
FREDDY:
Whose got a hose?
- 이건 누구건데?
- 가져가자
Whose is that right there?
Grab your hose!
실례할게요
Excuse me.
브라이언, 뒷 뜰에서
호스 가져와
MAN: Brian, your hose!
Backyard!
(camera shutter clicks)
바비
Barbie.
(camera shutter clicks)
일주일내내 비
한방울 안내렸어요
It hasn't rained in weeks.
성냥갑안에
갇힌 꼴이라고요
We're inside a damn tinderbox.
불이 다른 집에
옮겨 붙는다면
If those flames spread
to any of these other houses,
it's gonna take
체스터스 밀과 우릴
다 태울거에요
Chester's Mill and us with it.
정원에 호스가
없으신 분들께선
Hey, everybody who does
not have a garden hose,
양동이이나 항아리
I want you to go get a bucket,
get a pot,
쓰레기 통도 좋습니다
get-get a trash can, something.
뭐에라도 물을 받아오세요
Anything that can hold water.
Let's go.
가서 양동이를 가져오자고
MAN:
Let's go, get buckets!
- 사람 살려!
- 구해야겠어요
COGGINS: Help. Please help me!
Someone's inside.
린다!
Linda!
사람 살려요!
Somebody help me!
살려주세요!
Help!
(grunts)
(tires squeal)
계세요?
Anybody in here?!
(coughing)
저기요?
Hello?!
린다!
Linda!
- 괜찮아?
- 응
You okay?
(coughs) Yeah.
목사님이 서장님 댁에서
뭘하고 있었던거지?
What the hell was Coggins
doing in Duke's house?
모르겠어
짐은 어딨고?
I don't know.
Where did Jim go?
- 모르겠어
- 여기서 피하세요
I don't know.
PAUL: Get out of here, guys.
프로판 탱크가
집 옆에 있어요
There's a propane tank
next to the house.
맙소사, 프로판 탱크잖아
Oh, my God, that's
a propane tank!
여기서 모시고 나가자
Let's go, let's go,
get out of here.
어서, 부축해봐
Come on, get him out.
Go, go!
(multiple explosions)
불길이 거세네요
The flames are too high.
호스로도 안돼겠어요
The hoses aren't cutting it.
나무로 불이
옮겨붙고 있어요
JULIA: The fire is
spreading to the shrubs.
호스로 여기 좀 뿌려봐
Get another hose over there.
수압이 딸려
CAROLYN: There's not
enough water pressure.
브랜트우드에 살던 이웃들도
Can you imagine our
neighbors back in Brentwood
발벗고 도와줬을까?
helping out this way?
누가 옆집에 살았는지
기억도 안나
I don't even know
who our neighbors are.
서두르세요
FREDDY:
We got to go faster.
빅, 괜찮으세요?
Vic, you holding up all right?
네, 좋습니다
Come on, guys, that's right.
불이 꺼지려면
Just like that. We got to get
아직도 멀었습니다
more water on this thing,
all right? Come on.
멈추지 마시고
Keep going.
계속해서 물을 나르세요
Keep going, everyone.
We got to get more water.
어서요
Come on.
서루르세요
Faster, faster.
조금만 더요
LINDA:
Keep at it, people.
불이 담장에까지 옮겨붙었어요
The fire is spreading
to the fence.
집에도 옮겨붙겠어요
The house will be next.
부서장님, 도와주세요
Deputy, give me a hand.
담장 아래에 뿌려주세요
Over there, the
bottom of the fence.
물 더 받아오세요
Bottom of the fence.
Get more buckets!
물 더 가지고 오세요
Get some buckets in here.
차에도 옮겨붙었어요
The car's on fire.
다들 물러나세요
Guys, back, everybody back.
소용이 없겠어요
This isn't gonna work.
끝이 없겠어요
It's like playing Whac-a-Mole.
서장님 댁 부터
불을 끄지 않는다면요
As long as Duke's house
is burning,
불이 계속 옮겨붙겠어요
the fire is just gonna
keep jumping.
그랬다간 끝장나겠죠
Then it's over.
거기 비켜주세요
Or not. Hey, make some room!
어서요
Let's go!
길가에서 나오세요
Clear the street.
비킵시다
Get out of the street.
Let's go.
물러서주세요
FREDDY: Hey, back up.
Everybody get back.
다들 물러나주십쇼
Let's go.
빅 짐이 뭐하려는 거지?
What the hell is Big Jim doing?
제정신이야?
Is he insane?
서장님 댁을
박살낼 건가봐
He's gonna tear down
Duke's house.
(beeping)
(grunting, panting)
(metallic bang)
(lock clanks open)
어쩌다 그런거야?
What the hell happened to you?
네 남친 혼을
좀 내줬지
I took care of your boyfriend.
내 남친이라고?
My boyfriend?
너랑 떡쳤던 놈말야
The guy you've been screwing.
죽여버렸어
Killed him.
거짓말 마
No, you didn't.
죽었어, 앤지
He's dead, Angie.
네 몸에 손도 못댈거야
He's never gonna touch you ever.
널 못 믿겠어
I don't believe you.
왜?
Why not?
널 3학년 때부터
봐 왔는데
I've known you
since the third grade, James.
사람을 죽일
놈은 아냐
Even you couldn't do something
that terrible.
(chuckles softly)
내가 알던 앤지네
That's my Angie.
뭘 좀 가져왔어
I brought you something.
왜 이러는지
알게 될거야
This is what we're working for.
(lock clanks shut)
(sighs)
그런걸 생각해 내다니
Bucket brigade.
제법인데요
Pretty clever.
너무 멀쩡해 보이시네요
You weren't too shabby yourself.
고마워요
Why, thank you.
데일
Dale.
데일 바바라
Dale Barbara.
당신 이름이겠죠
I'm guessing that's you.
딱 걸렸네
Guilty.
어디서 찾으셨어요?
Where'd you find them?
그게 말이죠
Uh, you know what,
당신네 집 화장실
they were actually
just right there,
거울에 걸어뒀더라고요
where I left them, just hanging
over the mirror in you bathroom.
거길 제일
먼저 찾아봤는데
Huh. That's the first place
I checked.
못 보고 지나쳤나보네요
I must have missed them.
좀 어떤가?
How's he doing?
다 린다
부서장님 덕분입니다
It's lucky Linda got to him
when she did.
(groans)
연기를 좀 마셨지만
Took in a lot of smoke,
괜찮으실 겁니다
but I think
he's gonna pull through.
자리 좀 비켜주겠나?
Mind if I have a
moment with him?
도대체 왜 그런건가?
What the hell you thinking?
자네가 실수를
만회하라고 했잖나
You told me
to clean up our mess.
그래서 몽땅 태워버렸나?
You call this cleaning it up?
좀 어떠세요?
How is he?
운도 드럽게
좋은 놈이지
Well, there's someone up there
watching over him.
날 구해줘서 고맙네
Thank you for saving me.
(coughs)
천만에요
You're welcome,
근데 거기선
뭐하고 계셨던거에요?
but what in the world
were you doing in there?
(sighs)
난
I was, uh...
양복을 가지러 갔었어
...getting a suit
듀크의 장례식에 입으려고
for Duke's funeral.
불을 킨
(coughs)
I switched on a light,
후로는 기억이 안나더군
and then I can't really remember
the rest.
가스가 샜었나보네
Must have been a gas leak.
돔이 듀크의
뒷뜰을 가로질렀잖나
The dome's right there
in Duke's backyard.
그 때 가스관이 잘렸나봐
Probably, uh, severed a line.
괜찮으시다니
천만 다행이에요
Well, we're just all glad
you're okay, Reverend.
복 받을게야
Bless you, child.
(coughs)
린다
ROSE:
Linda,
목사님을 구해줘서 고마워요
thank you for saving
the reverend.
(indistinct chatter)
제 할 일을 한거죠
I'm just...
I'm just doing my job.
여러분도
수고가 많으셨습니다.
Thank you, everyone,
for a job well done.
당신이 없었으면
불가능 했을거에요, 빅 짐
Well, we couldn't have done
it without you, Big Jim.
Ah...
(indistinct chatter)
감사합니다만
BIG JIM:
I appreciate that,
저 혼자가 아닌
but, uh, this isn't about me.
여러분이 있어서 가능했습니다
It's about all of us.
마을이 위험한 상황에
We stood together,
shoulder to shoulder,
협동정신을 발휘했습니다
like a town should
in times like these.
체스터스 밀이
겪게 될 위기는
Now, this is not gonna be
the last crisis
여기서 끝이 아닐겁니다
that Chester's Mill faces,
또 다른
위기에 봉착하겠죠
but we'll get
through the next one
오늘 보여준 용맹함과
with the same courage
단결력으로 극복해 나갑시다
and solidarity
that we showed today.
수고하셨습니다
(applause)
Thank you all.
퍽이나 그러겠수다
Like hell we will.
뭘 꾸물거려
Go ahead,
잘했다고 자기자신을
칭찬해 주라고
pat yourselves on the backs
all you want,
근데 우린 좆됐잖아
but we're toast.
불은 껐다고 치자
Great, you can put out a fire.
어쩌라고?
So what?
저 물체 때문에
That thing...
연기가 통과를 못한다고
that thing is trapping smoke,
우린 여기 갇혔잖아
and there's no way out.
- 왜 그래
- 진정하세요, 폴
Hey, come on, man.
Take it easy, Paul.
물러서세요
Back up.
헤이
FREDDY:
Hey.
(low, indistinct talking)
진정하게 생겼냐고
Don't you tell me
to take it easy.
저자와 다를바가 없어
You know, you're just like him.
어디서 거짓말을 해
You know, like, you're
lying to these people,
괜찮아질 거라고 하는데
and you're promising that
everything is gonna be okay,
괜찮아질리가 없잖아!
and it's not gonna be okay!
이 물체는
This thing
절대로 없어지지 않을거야
is never gonna go away,
우린 다 죽은 목숨이라고!
and we're all gonna die!
폴, 그러지 말아요
(gunshots)
Paul, don't!
(crowd gasps)
안돼, 프레디!
Oh, no, no, Freddy!
프레디?
Freddy?
프레디, 정신차려
Freddy, stay with me.
프레디!
Freddy!
숨 쉬어봐, 어서
Breathe, stay with me, come on.
정신차려봐
Stay with me, Freddy.
프레디!
Freddy, Freddy.
Freddy!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com